

# DANIEL VALENTIN

UX Designer | Copenhagen | +45 22719298

#### o DETAILS o

#### Contact and address

Tiørnerækken 6, 2300 København +45 22719298

daniel.valentin.laursen@gmail.com dani763f.github.io/website/

# Age and nationality

28 years old Danish

Other

Drivers license

# • QUALIFICATIONS •

- · User research and analysis
- · Interaction design and information
- · Wireframing and prototyping
- · Usability testing
- · Visual design and layout
- · Design thinking
- · Stakeholder management and communication
- · Knowledge of design tools and frontend development
- · Accessibility and inclusive design principles
- · Familiarity with UI guidelines
- · Agile development methodologies
- · Team collaboration and communication

# LANGUAGE

Danish (First Janguage) English

# ○ FREE TIME ○

Open-Source software & Linux Selfhosting Computer Hardware Gaming Family





# ABOUT ME

My strength and passion is to understand, optimize and design IT solutions and processes. Whether the task is to implement, support or design new prototypes and solutions, for the last 5+ years I have worked professionally with the branches of IT in connection with my education from the IT University of Copenhagen. In my freetime i dabble with selfhosting, Linux and all things opensource

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### UX/IT Consultant, Racing Kids Freelance 2022 -

- Consulting and preparation of a new workflow for product import with the goal of time saving
- · Analysis of business needs and direct influence on technology stack
- · Took over the project from previous agency and facilitated the required knowledge management tasks
- · Presentation and learning, co-creation sessions with owner of Racing Kids

#### UX/IT Consultant, Hiorths Badehotel · Freelance 2018 - 2022

- IT support and process optimization tasks as well as maintenance and content for websites in wordpress
- · Provided consulting on user experience, interface and design to improve customer experience and enhance
- · Proven experience in web technologies, design and project management

#### IT Support Specialist at ITSS Group Technology, Nordea 2016 - 2019

- · Incident, knowledge and risk management tasks in various ERP systems.
- · Onboarding of new team members.
- Close collaboration with other IT departments in Denmark, Finland, Norway, Sweden, Poland and many other
- Maintain a high service level and meet SLA targets for the department.

#### Brand Ambassador, Gorm Larsen Nordic 2015 - 2016

- Sale and presentation of various hardware, including computers, printers, VR Headsets, smart phones and
- Bookkeeping of sales and interactions in Gorm Larsen's in-house CRM system.
- · Installation and responsibility for exhibition stands and other logistics in connection with conferences.
- · Mystery shopping and data collection

#### Webmaster, Restaurant Rusk · Freelance 2014 - 2018

- · Implemented web design improvements to increase user engagement and drive sales
- supported the online booking system
- Integrated website with social media and other platforms
- Implemented and maintained website security protocols and updates
- · Monitored website analytics and provided performance reports · Provided technical support and resolved website-related issues

# **EDUCATION**

### ${\sf MSc\cdot Digital\ Design\ and\ Interactive\ technologies,\ IT\ University\ of\ Copenhagen}$ 2021

- · Completed projects with Carlsberg, Nordea, Danish National Gallery and various other stakeholders

BSc · Global Business Informatics, IT University of Copenhagen 2018